[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "RP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 9, "question": "What on earth will Bill Maher say tonight?", "question_tokens": ["What", "on", "earth", "will", "Bill", "Maher", "say", "tonight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 10, "answer": "I want to feel like I broke into the studio and took over and made them mad.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "want", "to", "feel", "like", "I", "broke", "into", "the", "studio", "and", "took", "over", "and", "made", "them", "mad", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill Maher"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "PERCENT": ["9.2 percent"]}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CD", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", ":", "DT", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "The party out of power always threatens this, you know?", "question_tokens": ["The", "party", "out", "of", "power", "always", "threatens", "this", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "But isn't the reality, that with an election coming, just as the president hinted today, I mean if I was a Republican, the way to beat President Obama, the way that the job figures stand at the moment, 9.2 percent, the state of the economy generally, turmoil around the country continuing -- the way to probably beat him is to take him on on the economy.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "is", "n't", "the", "reality", ",", "that", "with", "an", "election", "coming", ",", "just", "as", "the", "president", "hinted", "today", ",", "I", "mean", "if", "I", "was", "a", "Republican", ",", "the", "way", "to", "beat", "President", "Obama", ",", "the", "way", "that", "the", "job", "figures", "stand", "at", "the", "moment", ",", "9.2", "percent", ",", "the", "state", "of", "the", "economy", "generally", ",", "turmoil", "around", "the", "country", "continuing", "--", "the", "way", "to", "probably", "beat", "him", "is", "to", "take", "him", "on", "on", "the", "economy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "It's not in their interest to do a deal, is it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "in", "their", "interest", "to", "do", "a", "deal", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "No probably about it.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "probably", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"], "PERCENT": ["3 percent"], "PERSON": ["Warren Buffett"]}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "Isn't it the Congress' job to present a jobs bill?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "it", "the", "Congress", "'", "job", "to", "present", "a", "jobs", "bill", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "Well, I like this quote from Warren Buffett who says the way to get rid of the deficit, we should pass a law that says any time there's a deficit of more than 3 percent of GDP, all sitting members of Congress are ineligible for reelection.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "like", "this", "quote", "from", "Warren", "Buffett", "who", "says", "the", "way", "to", "get", "rid", "of", "the", "deficit", ",", "we", "should", "pass", "a", "law", "that", "says", "any", "time", "there", "'s", "a", "deficit", "of", "more", "than", "3", "percent", "of", "GDP", ",", "all", "sitting", "members", "of", "Congress", "are", "ineligible", "for", "reelection", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "So it's all surprising to me that the people governing the country pander to that by this rhetoric of everything has to make a profit because that's the way you have a yardstick of success here, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["So", "it", "'s", "all", "surprising", "to", "me", "that", "the", "people", "governing", "the", "country", "pander", "to", "that", "by", "this", "rhetoric", "of", "everything", "has", "to", "make", "a", "profit", "because", "that", "'s", "the", "way", "you", "have", "a", "yardstick", "of", "success", "here", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "Well, if you're talking about social mobility, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "you", "'re", "talking", "about", "social", "mobility", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China"]}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "Why is it scary?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "it", "scary", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "Because it shows we're falling behind China.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "it", "shows", "we", "'re", "falling", "behind", "China", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "Can America afford to see everything economically, militarily and so on as a threat in the way it has before?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "America", "afford", "to", "see", "everything", "economically", ",", "militarily", "and", "so", "on", "as", "a", "threat", "in", "the", "way", "it", "has", "before", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", "CC", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "But we would have to reconfigure all of our priorities.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "we", "would", "have", "to", "reconfigure", "all", "of", "our", "priorities", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "Who's the threat that's going to invade us?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "the", "threat", "that", "'s", "going", "to", "invade", "us", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "Many Americans, it seems to me -- I mean you say this stuff and I bet you get deluged with people calling you unpatriotic, un-American.", "answer_tokens": ["Many", "Americans", ",", "it", "seems", "to", "me", "--", "I", "mean", "you", "say", "this", "stuff", "and", "I", "bet", "you", "get", "deluged", "with", "people", "calling", "you", "unpatriotic", ",", "un-American", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "But, I mean, is it time that America completely changed its philosophy on these things?", "question_tokens": ["But", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "is", "it", "time", "that", "America", "completely", "changed", "its", "philosophy", "on", "these", "things", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "What's patriotic is wanting your country to succeed.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "'s", "patriotic", "is", "wanting", "your", "country", "to", "succeed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "How many do the Chinese have?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "do", "the", "Chinese", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "None.", "answer_tokens": ["None", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Shanghai"]}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBN", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "How many?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "A hundred and 25,000 millionaires in Shanghai.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "hundred", "and", "25,000", "millionaires", "in", "Shanghai", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Palin or Bachmann?", "question_tokens": ["Palin", "or", "Bachmann", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "I would meet a gun to my head.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "meet", "a", "gun", "to", "my", "head", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bachmann"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "Is it possible in the current climate?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "possible", "in", "the", "current", "climate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Is America more or less racist now since Obama has been in power?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "America", "more", "or", "less", "racist", "now", "since", "Obama", "has", "been", "in", "power", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "RBR", "CC", "JJR", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "That's a great question.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "great", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "Are there other any of the Republican candidates so far that have emerged that you would see as potentially not life threatening?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "there", "other", "any", "of", "the", "Republican", "candidates", "so", "far", "that", "have", "emerged", "that", "you", "would", "see", "as", "potentially", "not", "life", "threatening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "RB", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "Well, you know, hopefully Mitt Romney.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "hopefully", "Mitt", "Romney", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jimmy Carter"]}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "Has there ever been a president in your lifetime who has been properly principled in your eyes?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "there", "ever", "been", "a", "president", "in", "your", "lifetime", "who", "has", "been", "properly", "principled", "in", "your", "eyes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "Jimmy Carter was an amazingly principled president.", "answer_tokens": ["Jimmy", "Carter", "was", "an", "amazingly", "principled", "president", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "It attracts criticism?", "question_tokens": ["It", "attracts", "criticism", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "Well, not that, is there's a kind of expectation from this mass populace that you have to do certain things.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "not", "that", ",", "is", "there", "'s", "a", "kind", "of", "expectation", "from", "this", "mass", "populace", "that", "you", "have", "to", "do", "certain", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "How do you think Obama is doing as president?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "think", "Obama", "is", "doing", "as", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "You know I love him.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "I", "love", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "Is it, though?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", ",", "though", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ",", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "What should he be doing right now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "should", "he", "be", "doing", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "If a Democrat gets in and we don't attempt Democratic policy.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "a", "Democrat", "gets", "in", "and", "we", "do", "n't", "attempt", "Democratic", "policy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "But what tag are you proudest of putting yourself to?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "tag", "are", "you", "proudest", "of", "putting", "yourself", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "JJS", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "I think I'm just practical.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "'m", "just", "practical", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "You hate their ideology, don't you think?", "question_tokens": ["You", "hate", "their", "ideology", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "But do you -- I mean you're a Democrat?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "--", "I", "mean", "you", "'re", "a", "Democrat", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "How would you describe yourself?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "describe", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "I mean I'm certainly more in line with their thinking.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "I", "'m", "certainly", "more", "in", "line", "with", "their", "thinking", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "Do you vote?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "vote", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "Democrat?", "question_tokens": ["Democrat", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "Almost always.", "answer_tokens": ["Almost", "always", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "Ever voted Republican?", "question_tokens": ["Ever", "voted", "Republican", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2000"], "PERSON": ["McCain"]}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "When?", "question_tokens": ["When", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "I voted for McCain in the 2000 primary.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "voted", "for", "McCain", "in", "the", "2000", "primary", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "Is part of it television cameras in the court?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "part", "of", "it", "television", "cameras", "in", "the", "court", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "Part of is that jury, trial of your peers.", "answer_tokens": ["Part", "of", "is", "that", "jury", ",", "trial", "of", "your", "peers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "People don't even get that, right?", "question_tokens": ["People", "do", "n't", "even", "get", "that", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "They cannot appreciate nuance.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "can", "not", "appreciate", "nuance", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "This is an apathetic, atheist, right?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "an", "apathetic", ",", "atheist", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "It's a combination of apathy and atheist, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "combination", "of", "apathy", "and", "atheist", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "No, that's not right at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "that", "'s", "not", "right", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "Is it bordering on any form of accuracy?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "bordering", "on", "any", "form", "of", "accuracy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "AHER: No.", "answer_tokens": ["AHER", ":", "No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "Then what happened?", "question_tokens": ["Then", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "I was never Jewish.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "never", "Jewish", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "Can you stop being a Catholic?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "stop", "being", "a", "Catholic", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "Where are you?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "I'm with him, 6.9.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "with", "him", ",", "6.9", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "How did your parents react to your ap-atheism?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "your", "parents", "react", "to", "your", "ap-atheism", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "When I was a kid, we went to church.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "I", "was", "a", "kid", ",", "we", "went", "to", "church", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ":", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "If you had prayed, would you have prayed for the kind of news cycle we have had, from Weiner-gate to Schwarzenegger-gate?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "had", "prayed", ",", "would", "you", "have", "prayed", "for", "the", "kind", "of", "news", "cycle", "we", "have", "had", ",", "from", "Weiner-gate", "to", "Schwarzenegger-gate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "It has been -- if there was a God for comedians, he may have been raining down upon us, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "has", "been", "--", "if", "there", "was", "a", "God", "for", "comedians", ",", "he", "may", "have", "been", "raining", "down", "upon", "us", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJR", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 638, "question": "Do you get as much fun of that now as you always used to?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "get", "as", "much", "fun", "of", "that", "now", "as", "you", "always", "used", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 639, "answer": "Much more, because I'm good at it now.", "answer_tokens": ["Much", "more", ",", "because", "I", "'m", "good", "at", "it", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "WRB", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 653, "question": "But do you feel a pressure, even when you're doing that, to be endlessly funny?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "feel", "a", "pressure", ",", "even", "when", "you", "'re", "doing", "that", ",", "to", "be", "endlessly", "funny", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 654, "answer": "I don't understand Twitter when people just tell you what they're doing.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "understand", "Twitter", "when", "people", "just", "tell", "you", "what", "they", "'re", "doing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 660, "question": "You don't troll for the ladies like Mr. Weiner?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "troll", "for", "the", "ladies", "like", "Mr.", "Weiner", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 661, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Weiner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 688, "question": "Aren't you going to get in trouble with your wife for talking about marriage this way?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "n't", "you", "going", "to", "get", "in", "trouble", "with", "your", "wife", "for", "talking", "about", "marriage", "this", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 689, "answer": "She would expect me to ask these kind of questions.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "would", "expect", "me", "to", "ask", "these", "kind", "of", "questions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 722, "question": "When you look at someone like Charlie Sheen, what do you honestly think of his behavioral pattern?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "at", "someone", "like", "Charlie", "Sheen", ",", "what", "do", "you", "honestly", "think", "of", "his", "behavioral", "pattern", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 723, "answer": "I know Charlie a bit.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "Charlie", "a", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 737, "question": "And is it true that you honestly believe you only go there for the food?", "question_tokens": ["And", "is", "it", "true", "that", "you", "honestly", "believe", "you", "only", "go", "there", "for", "the", "food", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 738, "answer": "I said that, it was a joke.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "said", "that", ",", "it", "was", "a", "joke", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 750, "question": "You went in the grotto?", "question_tokens": ["You", "went", "in", "the", "grotto", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 751, "answer": "I went in the grotto.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "went", "in", "the", "grotto", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 775, "question": "This job?", "question_tokens": ["This", "job", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 776, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 794, "question": "Is this part of the trick of show business, knowing when to leave the party?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "part", "of", "the", "trick", "of", "show", "business", ",", "knowing", "when", "to", "leave", "the", "party", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 795, "answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Larry"]}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 796, "question": "Being able to choose it -- have your own destiny?", "question_tokens": ["Being", "able", "to", "choose", "it", "--", "have", "your", "own", "destiny", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 797, "answer": "But I didn't think Larry was diminished in any way.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "I", "did", "n't", "think", "Larry", "was", "diminished", "in", "any", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 806, "question": "Is that true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 807, "answer": "Never.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]